Finding Aid for Philip A. Hart Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Subject files, 1959-1976; 96 linear feet
  - 1965
    - Health
      - Smoking, Cigarette Advertising (Box 154)
      - Water Fluoridation (Box 154)
    - Highways
      - Michigan
        - 1964 (Box 154)
        - 1965 (Box 154)
        - 8 Mile Road (Box 154)
        - Federal Funds (Box 154)
        - Proposed Route I-75 (Box 154)
        - Relocating Business Highway (Box 154)
        - Rite of Way, Condemnation Stat. (Box 154)
        - Route I-696, Oak Park (Box 154)
        - Secondary Roads (Box 154)
        - Shoreline Drive, Munising to Grand Marais, 2 folders (Box 154)
        - Shoreline Scenic (Box 154)
        - Signs (Box 154)
        - Tolls, Blue Water Bridge (Box 154)
        - Tolls, Mackinac Bridge, 2 folders (Box 154)
        - Traffic Safety (Box 154)
      - Relocating Business Highway Displacement (Box 154)
      - Right of Way, Condemnation Statutes (empty) (Box 154)
      - Scenic Highway, Upper Peninsula (Box 154)
      - Signs (Box 154)
      - Tolls, Interstate System of Highways (Box 154)
      - US, 1965 (Box 154)
      - US, Interstate (Box 154)
      - US, Interstate, Facilities (Box 154)
      - US, National, Scenic (Box 154)
      - US, Safety (Box 154)
      - US, 1964 (Box 154)
    - Housing
      - Project Detroit "City of Tomorrow" (Box 155)
      - Public Housing Project, Ypsilanti (Box 155)
      - Urban Renewal
        - Benton Harbor (Box 155)
        - Big Rapids (Box 155)
        - Cheboygan (Box 155)
        - Dearborn Heights (Box 155)
        - Detroit (Box 155)
        - Grand Rapids (Box 155)
        - Hamtramck (Box 155)
        - Highland Park (Box 155)
        - Jackson, 2 folders (Box 155)
        - Lansing (Box 155)
        - Lincoln Park (Box 155)
        - Marquette (Box 155)
        - Michigan City, Indiana (Box 155)
        - Muskegon Heights (Box 155)
        - St. Clair Shores (Box 155)
        - St. Ignace (Box 155)
        - Wayne (Box 155)
        - Ypsilanti (Box 155)
    - Indians
      - General (Box 155)
      - Bay Mills Community (Box 155)
      - St. Labre (Box 155)
    - Labor
      - Bracero (Box 155)
      - Bracero, 1 Year Extension, 1963 (Box 155)
      - Bracero, Pickle Industry (Box 155)
      - Bracero, Study of (Box 155)
      - Discrimination, Equal Employment Opportunities (Box 155)
      - Strikes
        - Can (Box 155)
        - Docks (Box 155)
        - R/R (Box 155)
        - Steel (Box 155)
        - Taft/Hartley (Box 155)
        - Taft/Hartley, Compulsory Arbitration (Box 155)
      - Unions (Box 155)
    - Natural Resources
      - Conservation
        - General (Box 155)
        - Channel Island (Box 155)
        - Fish and Wildlife (Box 155)
        - Grand Metro Area (Box 155)
        - Palisades Park (Box 155)
        - Refuge (Box 155)
      - Forestry, Timber (Box 155)
      - Gas, Natural (Box 155)
      - National Forests
        - Hiawatha (Box 155)
        - Huron (Box 155)
        - Huron/Manistee (Box 155)
        - Ottawa (Box 155)
        - Selway-Bitterroot (Box 155)
        - Superior National Forest, Minn. (Box 155)
      - National Parks
        - General (Box 155)
        - Everglades (Box 155)
        - Great Smokies (Box 155)
        - Isle Royale (Box 155)
        - Roads (Box 155)
      - Water
        - Dam (Box 155)
        - Water Level (Box 155)
        - Water Levels, Great Lakes Compact (Box 155)
        - Water Pollution
          - General (Box 155)
          - Bear River (Box 155)
          - Detergent (Box 155)
          - Detroit River (Box 155)
          - Lake Erie, Lake Huron (Box 155)
          - Laboratory, Ann Arbor (Box 155)
          - Pere Marquette River (Box 155)
          - Waste Treatment Plants (Box 155)
    - Post Office
      - Mail Censorship (Box 155)
      - Objectionable Mailings
        - General (Box 155)
        - Unsolicited Merchandise (Box 155)
        - Unsolicited Political Propaganda (Box 155)
    - Power
      - Hydro-Electric Rampart Dam (Box 155)
      - REA (Box 155)
      - REA, Michigan (Box 155)
      - REA, Upper Peninsula (Box 155)
    - President, Office of
      - Criticism (Box 155)
      - Succession (Box 155)
    - Recreation
      - AAU/NCAA Dispute (Box 156)
      - Hunting (Box 156)
      - Olympics (Box 156)
      - Parks, Michigan (Box 156)
    - Refugees and Escapees
      - Chinese (Box 156)
      - Cuban (Box 156)
    - Science/Research
      - Medical (Box 156)
      - Medical, Kidney Disease (Box 156)
      - Medical Smoking (Box 156)
      - NASA, Rocket Experiment (Box 156)
    - Security/Internal
      - General, 1965 (Box 156)
      - Communism
        - Communism Party (Box 156)
        - Communism Party, Schools (Box 156)
        - House Un-American Activities Committee (Box 156)
        - Infiltration in School (Box 156)
        - Infiltration in South, Civil Rights (Box 156)
        - Senate Internal, Security Subcommittee (Box 156)
      - Far Right
        - General (Box 156)
        - John Birch Society (Box 156)
        - Right Wing Groups "Watch Washington Club" (Box 156)
        - Young American for Freedom (Box 156)
      - Foreign Agents, Registration (Box 156)
      - Loyalty, Security Risks, Otepka, Unanswered Non-Mich. Mail (Box 156)
      - Oath of Allegiance (Box 156)
      - Subversive Activities, Literature (Box 156)
    - Senate
      - Investigation Baker (Box 156)
      - Majority Whip (Box 156)
      - Rules, Reform (Box 156)
    - Supreme Court
      - Prayer, Schools (Box 156)
      - Reapportionment, 2 folders (Box 156)
    - Taxes
      - Excise (Box 156)
      - Exemptions, Organizations (Box 156)
      - Internal Revenue Code (Box 156)
      - Michigan, State of (Box 156)
      - Personal Deductions (Box 156)
    - Treaties
      - Hague Protocol, Amendment to Warsaw Convention (Box 156)
      - Human Rights Convention (Box 156)
      - NATO, Nuclear Fleet (Box 156)
      - US/USSR Consular Convention (Box 156)
    - United Nations
      - Admittance, Red China (Box 156)
      - Assessments (Box 156)
      - Organization (Box 156)
    - Welfare, Social
      - Capital Punishment (Box 156)
      - Elder Care (Box 156)
      - Frauds, Deceptions (Box 156)
      - Medicare (Kerr-Mills) (Box 156)
      - Moral Welfare re Pornographic Material (Box 156)
      - Population Control (Box 156)
      - Population, Large Families, POLF (Box 156)
  - 1966
    - Agriculture
      - Beans, 1966 (Box 156)
      - Cherries, 1966 (Box 156)
      - Cherries, Referendum on Marketing Order (Box 156)
      - Farm Income (Box 156)
      - Farm Program, Emergency Feed Grain (Box 156)
      - National Committee on Food Marketing Report to Farmers, 2 folders (Box 156)
    - Appropriations, Agriculture (Box 156)
    - Armed Services
      - Criticism, McNamara (Box 156)
      - D.O.D. Directives (Box 156)
      - Draft (Box 157)
      - Draft Deferment (Box 157)
      - Facility, Phasing Out, Consolidation, Kincheloe A.F. Base (Box 157)
      - Preparedness
        - Draft
          - June-December 1966 (Box 157)
          - Classification, Viet Nam protest (Box 157)
          - Women (Box 157)
        - Equipment
          - Viet Nam (Box 157)
          - Viet Nam, Dri-Slide (Box 157)
        - Korea (Box 157)
        - Training/Manpower, 2 folders (Box 157)
        - Viet Nam
          - General (Box 157)
          - Allies (Box 157)
          - Black Market (Box 157)
          - Communist Troops (Box 157)
          - Herbicides, etc. (Box 157)
          - Statistics (Box 157)
      - Reorganization (Box 157)
      - Selective Services Draft, 1966 (Box 157)
      - Weapons (Box 157)
      - Weapons, Phasing Out (Box 157)
    - Atomic Energy
      - Facilities (Box 157)
      - Nuclear Proliferation (Box 157)
    - Budget, 1967 (Box 157)
    - Civil Rights
      - General (Box 157)
      - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 157)
      - Arkansas (Box 157)
      - Black Power (Box 157)
      - Communist Party, Non-Membership Affirmation (Box 157)
      - Community Relations Service (Box 157)
      - Fair Housing (Box 157)
      - Freedom of Speech (Box 157)
      - Freedom of Speech, Protection of Dissenter (Box 157)
      - Freedoms Guaranteed by Constitution (Box 157)
      - Michigan (Box 157)
      - Religious Freedom, Prayer in School (Box 157)
      - South (Box 157)
      - Voting Rights Act (Box 157)
    - Commerce
      - General
        - Census, Manufacturer's (Box 157)
        - Commercial Fisheries (Box 157)
      - Communication
        - Radio
          - Fairness Doctrine (Box 157)
          - Radio Hanoi Sedition Possibility (Box 157)
        - TV
          - Caliber of Program (Box 157)
          - Fairness Doctrine (Box 157)
          - Microwave Relays, CATV (Box 157)
      - Tariffs
        - General (Box 157)
        - Free Trade, Canada-US (Box 157)
        - GATT-General Agreement for Tariffs and Trade (Box 157)
      - Trade
        - Common Market (Box 157)
        - Duty, Offset Operation. Canada, Auto (Box 157)
        - Free World Comm., Viet Nam (Box 157)
        - Imports, Restrictions (Box 157)
        - International, Michigan (Box 157)
        - Iron Curtain, Countries (Box 157)
        - Subsidy, Tobacco (Box 157)
      - Transportation
        - Air, Facilities, Jim Robbins Airport-Troy (Box 158)
        - R/R Mergers (Box 158)
        - Water
          - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 158)
          - Tolls, Soo Locks (Box 158)
          - Tolls, St. Lawrence (Box 158)
          - Trade Routes (Great Lakes) (Box 158)
    - Defense, National
      - Arms, Disarmament (Box 158)
      - Essential, Industry Rating (Box 158)
      - Strategic Material, Sale of (Box 158)
      - Strategic Material, Sale of Copper (Box 158)
      - UFO, Investigations Faci (Box 158)
      - UFO, Unidentified Flying Objects (Box 158)
    - Economy, National
      - Debt, Foreign Indebtedness (Box 158)
      - Free Enterprise Society (Box 158)
      - "Great Society" (Box 158)
      - Inflation (Box 158)
      - Loans (Box 158)
      - Loans ARA (Box 158)
      - Upcap (Box 158)
      - War on Poverty
        - Community Action Program (Box 158)
        - Criticism of (Box 158)
        - EDA, Northboard (Box 158)
        - Job Corps (Box 158)
        - Neighborhood Youth Corps (Box 158)
        - NORCAP (Box 158)
        - Program (Box 158)
        - Program, Criticism of (Box 158)
        - Project Head Start (Box 158)
        - TAP, Legal Services (Box 158)
        - Upward Bound (Box 158)
    - Education
      - Education System
        - Michigan (Box 158)
        - Michigan, endorsement of (Box 158)
        - School Lunch Program (Box 158)
      - Federal Funds and Assistance
        - General (Box 158)
        - Handicapped (Box 158)
    - Foreign Relations
      - General, 1966 (Box 159)
      - Africa
        - Apartheid (Box 159)
        - Rhodesia (Box 159)
        - South Africa (Box 159)
      - AID, Agency for International Development
        - General (Box 159)
        - Policy, Criticism of (Box 159)
      - Asia
        - Cambodia (Box 159)
        - Communist China (Box 159)
        - India (Box 159)
        - Thailand (Box 159)
        - Viet Nam
          - Christmas Bombing (Box 159)
          - Christmas Cease Fire (Box 159)
          - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 159)
          - Easter Cease Fire (Box 159)
          - Economic Aid (Box 159)
          - Hanoi Bombings (Box 159)
          - Peace Offer (Box 159)
          - Senator Fulbright's Remark (Box 159)
          - U.N. Security Council (Box 159)
          - For Aid (Box 159)
          - For Aid, Asia, India (Box 159)
          - Military, Build-up (Box 159)
          - Near and Middle East, United Arab Rep. (Box 159)
    - Health
      - Air Pollution, Car Exhaust (Box 159)
      - Fluoridation, Water (Box 159)
      - Food and Drug, DDT levels (Box 159)
      - Food and Drug, Krebiozan (Box 159)
      - Grants, Mental Health, Grand Rapids Child Guidance Clinic (Box 159)
    - Highways-Michigan
      - 1966 (Box 159)
      - Access Roads (Box 159)
      - Federal Funds (Box 159)
      - I-275 (Box 159)
      - Proposed Route, I-696 (Box 159)
      - Proposed Route, I-75 (Box 159)
      - Proposed Route, I-94 (Box 159)
      - Relocating Homes, Michigan (Box 159)
      - Rite of Way (Box 159)
      - Secondary Roads (Box 159)
      - Signs (Box 159)
      - Tolls, Blue Water Bridge (Box 159)
      - Tolls, Mackinac Bridge (Box 159)
      - Traffic Safety (Box 159)
    - Housing
      - Financing Planning Assistance (Box 160)
      - Financing Subsidies (Box 160)
      - Financing Subsidies, Neighborhood Centers (Box 160)
      - Financing Subsidies, NORCAP (Box 160)
      - Low Rent Housing
        - Clinton Township (Box 160)
        - Elderly (Box 160)
        - Elderly, Pontiac (Box 160)
        - Migrant Workers (Box 160)
      - Migrant Labor (Box 160)
      - Public Housing
        - Flint (Box 160)
        - Lansing (Box 160)
        - Lincoln Park (Box 160)
      - Urban Renewal
        - General (Box 160)
        - Criticism (Box 160)
        - Demonstration Cities (Box 160)
        - Detroit (Box 160)
        - Garden City (Box 160)
    - Indians
      - 1966 (Box 160)
      - Claims Creek (Box 160)
      - St. Labre Mission (Box 160)
    - Labor
      - Bracero (Box 160)
      - Bracero, Pickle Industry (Box 160)
      - Bracero, Study of (Box 160)
      - Employ, Race Reference (Box 160)
      - Employ, Replacement by Cubans (Box 160)
      - Retirement System, Private Industry (Box 160)
      - Retirement System, R/R (Box 160)
      - Strikes
        - General (Box 160)
        - Airlines (Box 160)
        - Canadian R/R (Box 160)
        - GE (Box 160)
        - New York Transit Strike (Box 160)
        - R/R (Box 160)
        - Wage Dispute (Box 160)
      - Unions (Box 160)
      - Unions, Recognition of (Box 160)
      - Wages
        - Farm Labor, Increased Cost (Box 160)
        - Guidelines (Box 160)
        - Minimum (Box 160)
        - Minimum, Michigan (Box 160)
        - Minimum Youth Employment (Box 160)
        - Overtime (Box 160)
      - Working Conditions (Box 160)
    - Land
      - Acquisition, State, Gull Island (Box 160)
      - Surveys (Box 160)
    - Natural Resources
      - Conservation
        - General (Box 160)
        - Fish and Wildlife (Box 160)
        - Fish and Wildlife, Deer (Box 160)
        - Redwoods (Box 160)
      - Forestry, Facilities, Houghton (Box 160)
      - National Forests, Manistee, Porter-Mulder (Box 160)
      - National Forests, Ottawa (Sylvania Tract) (Box 160)
      - Water
        - Geographic Names (Box 160)
        - Great Lakes Commission (Box 160)
        - Inter Joint Commission (Box 160)
        - Level, Great Lakes (Box 160)
        - Level, Lake Michigan/Illinois River, Juris of (Box 160)
        - Pollution, General
          - Detroit River (Box 160)
          - Great Lakes (Box 160)
          - Lake Erie (Box 160)
          - Rivers, Lakes (Box 160)
        - Supply (Box 160)
    - Post Office
      - Objectionable Mailings (Box 160)
      - Objectionable Mailings, Political Propaganda (Box 160)
    - Power
      - Hydro-Electric
        - Bridge Canyon (Grand Canyon) (Box 160)
        - Rampart Dam (Box 160)
    - President
      - Criticism of (Box 160)
      - Death/Kennedy, Warren Commission (Box 160)
      - Health Condition of (Box 160)
      - Req. Messages (Box 160)
      - Vice-President, Criticism of (Box 160)
    - Recreation
      - Federal Assistance (Box 161)
      - Parks, Michigan (Box 161)
      - Recreational Resources, Michigan (Box 161)
    - Refugees/Escapees
      - Chinese (Box 161)
      - Cuban (Box 161)
      - Vietnam (Box 161)
    - Security, Internal
      - CIA (Box 161)
      - Communism (Box 161)
      - Communism, Registration of Members (Box 161)
      - Communism, Registration of Organizations (Box 161)
      - Communism, Senate Internal Security, Subcommittee (Box 161)
      - Communist Party, Infiltration in Civil Rights Activities (Box 161)
      - "Far Rightist's and Birchers" (Box 161)
      - Far Rite, John Birch Society (Box 161)
      - Far Rite Groups (Box 161)
      - Far Rite Publications (Box 161)
      - House Un-American Activities Committee (Box 161)
      - Logan Act (Box 161)
      - Surveillance Individuals Abroad (Box 161)
      - Subversive Activities (Box 161)
    - Senate
      - Committee Hearings, Criticism of (Box 161)
      - Committee, Watch Dog Committee (Box 161)
      - Filibuster (Box 161)
      - Investigation, Senator Dodd (Box 161)
      - Memorial, McNamara (Box 161)
      - Reforms, Organization (Box 161)
      - Reforms, TV Coverage (Box 161)
      - Rules (Box 161)
      - Rules, Reform (Box 161)
      - Standard and Conduct (Box 161)
    - Supreme Court
      - Decisions (Box 161)
      - Justice Douglas (Box 161)
      - Reapportionment (Box 161)
      - School Prayer (Box 161)
    - Taxes
      - Income
        - Deductions/Ed. Expenses (Box 161)
        - Deductions/Exemptions (Box 161)
        - Personal (Box 161)
        - Return to Community (Box 161)
    - Treaties
      - Geneva Agreement (Box 161)
      - Hague Protocol Amend to Warsaw Convention (Box 161)
      - Human Rights Convention (Box 161)
      - Panama Canal (Box 161)
      - UN Convention on Racial Discrimination (Box 161)
      - US/USSR Consular Convention (Box 161)
    - United Nations
      - Red China, Admittance of (Box 161)
      - Support of (Box 161)
      - US Ambassador (Box 161)
    - Welfare, Social
      - Capital Punishment (Box 161)
      - Crime Punishment, 2 folders (Box 161)
      - Medicare (Box 161)
      - Medicare, Michigan (Box 161)
      - Population, Control of (Box 161)
      - Pornographic Material (Box 161)
      - Research, War Toys, Effect of (Box 161)
      - Riots (Box 161)
      - Riots, Benton Harbor (Box 161)
  - 1967
    - Agriculture
      - Beans (Box 161)
      - Dairies (Box 161)
      - Farm Program (Box 161)
      - Food, Food Stamp Plan (Box 161)
      - Grading and Inspecting (Box 161)
    - Appropriations
      - Forest Engineering (Box 161)
      - HEW (Box 161)
      - Interior (Box 161)
    - Armed Services
      - Appropriations, Ration (Box 162)
      - Awards (Box 162)
      - Benefits, Dependents (Box 162)
      - Civilian Marksmanship (Box 162)
      - Criticism, Sea Bee Mailer (Box 162)
      - Defectors/POW (Box 162)
      - D.O.D. Directives
        - General (Box 162)
        - COLA (Box 162)
        - Court Martial (Box 162)
        - Desegregation (Box 162)
        - Immoral Activities (Box 162)
        - Pay (Box 162)
        - Reserve Cruises (Box 162)
      - Preparedness Draft
        - General (Box 162)
        - Anti-Draft Seminar (Box 162)
        - Conscientious Objectors (Box 162)
        - Deferment (Box 162)
        - Draft Dodgers (Box 162)
        - Reserves, Call-up (Box 162)
        - Women (Box 162)
      - Preparedness Equipment, V.M., Dri-slide Oil (Box 162)
      - Preparedness Survival Training (Box 162)
      - Preparedness Thailand (Box 162)
      - Preparedness Training/Manpower
        - Assignment Policy
          - General (Box 162)
          - Sole Son (Box 162)
          - Two Sons in Service (Box 162)
        - Reserve (Box 162)
        - ROTC (Box 162)
      - Preparedness Viet Nam
        - General (Box 162)
        - Black Market (Box 162)
        - Enlist Extension, 2 folders (Box 162)
        - Equipment (Box 162)
        - Herbicides, etc. (Box 162)
        - Military Personnel Policies (Box 162)
        - Weapons (Box 162)
      - Reorganization National Guard (Box 162)
      - Right of Appeal (Box 162)
    - Atomic Energy
      - Facilities 200 BEV, Illinois (Box 162)
      - Facilities Licenses (Box 162)
      - Facilities Michigan (Box 162)
      - Nuclear Power Waste (Box 162)
      - Nuclear Testing Nevada (Box 162)
    - Budget (Box 162)
    - Civil Disorders
      - General (Box 162)
      - Detroit, July 25, 1967 (Box 162)
      - Federal Assistance (Box 162)
      - Federal Intervention (Box 162)
      - Michigan
        - General (Box 162)
        - Detroit (Box 162)
        - Hearings (Box 162)
        - Insurance (Box 162)
        - Law Enforcement (Box 162)
        - Non-Michigan (Box 162)
        - State Intervention (Box 162)
    - Civil Rights
      - 1967 (Box 162)
      - Community Relations (Box 162)
      - Discrimination (Box 162)
      - Discrimination Investigation of Federal Agencies (Box 162)
      - Draft Board, Discrimination (Box 162)
      - Fair Housing (Box 162)
      - Freedoms Guaranteed by Constitution (Box 162)
      - Freedoms Guaranteed by Constitution Dissent (Box 162)
      - Individual Liberties, 2 folders (Box 162)
      - Jury Discrimination (Box 162)
      - Loyalty Oath (Box 162)
      - Michigan (Box 162)
      - Racism (Box 162)
      - Religious Freedom, Prayer in School (Box 162)
      - South (Box 162)
    - Commerce
      - Census (Box 163)
      - Census, racial (Box 163)
      - Communications
        - FCC (Box 163)
        - Movies, Caliber of (Box 163)
        - Radio, Emergency Broadcast System (Box 163)
        - Radio, Fairness Doctrine (Box 163)
        - TV, Educational (Box 163)
        - TV, Equal Time-Fairness (Box 163)
        - TV, Microwave Relays (CATV) (Box 163)
      - Consumer Interest (Box 163)
      - Consumer Interest, Standard (Box 163)
      - Fisheries (Box 163)
      - Fisheries, Great Lakes (Box 163)
      - Tariffs, G.A.T.T. (Box 163)
      - Tariffs, G.A.T.T., Automotive Industry (Box 163)
      - Trade
        - Barriers (Box 163)
        - Common Market (Box 163)
        - Communist Countries (Box 163)
        - Communist Countries, Competition with (Box 163)
        - Export, Foreign Credit Insurance (Box 163)
        - Free World Comm., Vietnam (Box 163)
        - Imports
          - General (Box 163)
          - Duty Rates (Box 163)
          - Foreign Trade Zone (Box 163)
          - License (Box 163)
          - Quota (Box 163)
          - Restrictions (Box 163)
      - Transportation
        - Air
          - FAA (Box 163)
          - Facilities
            - Antrim Airport (Box 163)
            - Cheboygan Airport (Box 163)
            - Detroit Metro-Wayne Co. (Box 163)
            - Escanaba Airport (Box 163)
            - Kellogg Field (Box 163)
            - Traverse City Airport (Box 163)
            - West Branch (Box 163)
        - Alan S. Boyd (Box 163)
        - Mass, Michigan (Box 163)
        - Water
          - Ships
            - Pilotage (Box 163)
            - Safety Standards (Box 163)
          - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 163)
          - Trade Routes -- Great Lakes (Box 163)
    - Defense, National
      - ABM Defense (Box 163)
      - Anti Missile System (Box 163)
      - Arms, Control and Disarmament (Box 163)
      - Civil Defense (Box 163)
      - Defense Spending (Box 163)
      - Emergency Executive Orders (Box 163)
      - National Guard (Box 163)
      - Nuclear Test Ban (Box 163)
      - Strategic Material, Sale of (Box 163)
      - UFO, Unidentified Flying Objects (Box 163)
      - WWIII (Box 163)
    - Economy, National
      - Debt, Foreign Indebtedness (Box 164)
      - EDA, Copper Peak Ski Flying (Box 164)
      - Federal Aid to Communications, Upper Great Lakes Regional Commission (Box 164)
      - "Great Society" (Box 164)
      - Loans, EDA, Copper Peak Ski Flying Hill Project (Box 164)
      - Problems (Box 164)
      - War on Poverty
        - Community Action (Box 164)
        - Community Action, Four Cap (Box 164)
        - Criticism of (Box 164)
        - Five Cap (Box 164)
        - Foster Grandparents (Box 164)
        - Grant Announcement (Box 164)
        - Guidelines (Box 164)
        - Human Resources, Development (Box 164)
        - Job Corps (Box 164)
        - Judicare Program (Box 164)
        - KAL-CAP (Box 164)